You attended the Satipatthana course to understand it directly in the words of Buddha.
Not that in the first Satipatthana course one understands everything.
As I said, every word will be clear when you reach the final goal.
But it will become clearer and clearer as you practice.
So many questions keep coming, I smile at the questions, they are good.
After all, human being is a rational being.
He wants to rationalize whatever one is doing.
Yes, it is good, one should do.
But questions, somebody who has passed through that process, it looks like a child's question.
When people ask, the same very persons who are asking this question,
practicing further, further, further, the answer will come.
And the answer that will come by your own...